<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="yukinoQuotesTitle">Yukinoshita Yukino Quotes</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes1">1) Nobody is perfect, after all. People are weak, ugly, and they get
        jealous and try to bring others down. Oddly enough, the better you are, the harder it is to live.
        That\'s why I\'m going to change this world and the people in it.</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes2">2) We won\'t give a fish to a starving man, but we will teach
        him to fish and be independent.</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes3">3) The only way to solve a problem is hard work. [&#8230;] Those who
        can\'t even work hard don\'t deserve to envy those with talent. Those who cannot succeed cannot
        imagine the effort of those who do, and thus cannot succeed themselves.</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes4">4) (To Yumiko) Talking ? Was that what you call a conversation ? It looked more like
        you forcing your own opinions on someone else. [&#8230;] I\'m afraid I\'m not well-acquainted with your
        ecosystem. Just now, I thought you were menacing me like a troglodyte. It\'s all well and good to posture
        and play king of the hill, but please contain yourself to your own territory. Like your make-up,
        it\'s easy to wipe away.</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes5">5) All the girls in school grew desperate to eliminate me, but none of
        them tried to improve themselves to surpass me. The fools.</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes6">6) If all you\'re good for is breathing in and out, then that
        air conditioner over there is far superior to you.</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes7">7) (To Hachiman &amp; Yui) If it\'s over, then can\'t you just start again ? After all, neither of
        you were wrong. [&#8230;] If neither of you are wrong, then there is no reason to argue to begin with.
        That way, you can both begin again, properly.</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes8">8) That\'s just your persecution complex. Maybe you feel like
    I\'m looking down on you because you\'re simply conscious of your own inferiority?</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes9">9) Knowing each other is one thing, but understanding is an altogether
        different matter.</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes10">10) (To Hachiman) I thought we both hated superficiality more than anything.
        [&#8230;] You\'ve always been avoiding the problem at hand. Weren\'t you the one who called such
        superficiality meaningless?</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes11">11) If this is all it takes to tear us apart, then maybe we weren\'t
        all that close to begin with.</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes12">12) (To the student council) If all you want to do is playing pretend, could you take it elsewhere ?
        You\'ve done nothing but spout meaningless prattle. Is pretending to be upper management with words you
        just picked up that much fun ? Mistaking vague statements for actual communication and understanding,
        while never lifting a finger&#8230; How could that lead to any progress ? It will never create anything,
        never improve anything, and never help anything. It\'s nothing but a sham.</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes13">13) So long as people close to me understand, I\'ll be fine.</string>
    <string name="yukinoQuotes14">14) Nyaaaa~</string>

    <string name="hachimanQuoteTitle">Hikigaya Hachiman Quotes</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes1">1) Youth is both a lie, and a form of evil. Those who sing the praises of youth are deluding
        themselves and those around them. They immerse themselves in an environment where their delusions are reaffirmed. In the
        name of the word \"youth\", they can distort any reasonable explanation or commonly accepted idea to their liking. To them,
        lies, secrets, guilt, and even failure are all just the spices of youth. For instance, if failure were a sign of youth, one
        could argue that a human being who fails to make friends is also at the heart of youth. However he wouldn\'t acknowledge that.
        It\'s all just double standards. Here\'s my conclusion : Fools who enjoy their youth can all go to hell.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes2">2) Changing, being changed. I don’t want anyone else telling me what to do.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes3">3) Hard work betrays none, but dreams betray many. Working hard alone doesn\'t assure
        you that you\'ll achieve your dreams. Actually there are more cases where you don\'t. Even so, working hard and
        achieving something is some consolation at least.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes4">4) Animals naturally form packs. Carnivores form social hierarchies within
        their packs. Those that fail to become alphas harbor the burden of failure until they die. I\'m sure the herbivores feel
        guilt as they sacrifice their comrades to evade their predators and live on. In this world, forming packs yields no benefit
        for the individual. Thus, I choose the way of the solitary bear, which does not form packs. The bear finds no anxiety in
        living alone. He is proud. He is a lone wolf. Furthermore, they hibernate in the winter. How wonderful that must be. There
        is no doubt in my mind. In my next life, I want to be a bear.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes5">5) I hate nice girls. Just exchanging pleasantries with them makes me curious, and texting each
        other makes me feel restless. If I get a call, for the rest of the day, I keep checking my call history with a stupid grin
        on my face. But I know the truth. They\'re just being nice. Anyone nice to me is nice to others too. But I always find myself
        on the verge of forgetting that. If the truth is a cruel mistress, then a lie must be a nice girl. And so, niceness is a lie.
        I would always hold expectations. I would always misunderstand. At some point, I stopped hoping. An experienced loner never
        falls for the same trap twice. A lone warrior, surviving hundreds of battles. When it comes to losing, I\'m the strongest.
        That\'s why I will always hate nice girls.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes6">6) This girl has already given up. Even if she changes herself, the world won\'t change. People
        estimate the value of other people based on prejudices and impressions. Loners are made loners through coercion. If you try
        to work hard, or stand out, It\'ll be turned into material for an attack. Those are the corrupt rules in the childhood
        kingdom. […] Question : The world won\'t change. You must change yourself. Now, how should you change yourself? Answer :
        Become the god of a new world.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes7">7) When humans are faced with truly terrifying circumstances, they don\'t think about other
        people around them. They\'re even willing to sacrifice those around themselves. By exposing that unsightly part of them,
        they can no longer get along.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes8">8) I like myself. Up to this point, I\'ve never felt like I hated myself. My high basic specs
        and my not-half-bad looks. Even my pessimistic, realistic thinking. I accepted all of it and didn\'t hate myself. But it
        appears I may come to hate myself for the first time. From my point of view, Yukinoshita Yukino… is always beautiful and
        honest. She never tells a lie. Even without a crutch, she keeps standing. I\'m sure that\'s the Yukinoshita Yukino I was
        attracted to. I selfishly hope and push for my dream. I selfishly worried about what she knew, and then I selfishly fell
        into despair. Even though I admonished myself over and over again, in the end, it didn\'t get better. Even Yukinoshita
        Yukino lies. The fact that I couldn\'t pardon such an obvious fact, I hate it.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes9">9) Is it wrong to do stuff by yourself? If someone worked hard on their own until now,
        why do they have to face rejection here? That\'s something I cannot forgive.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes10">10) They say that if you change yourself, you\'ll change the world. but that\'s a complete
        lie. They\'re just forcing you to compromise, by feeding you a convenient little fib.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes11">11) Well, they say the character for \"person\" (人) looks like two people supporting
        each other, but doesn\'t it look like one side is relying on the other to hold them up? I think approving of someone
        becoming a sacrifice is the general idea behind \"person\".</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes12">12) Having people acknowledge your existence is a wonderful thing.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes13">13) \"The important thing is to participate.\" The father of the modern Olympics, Baron Pierre
        de Coubertin, used these words in a well known speech. However, these words are often abused for the sake of forcing
        participation, and used as the threatening phrase. In this world, there are many situations in which participation is
        pointless. If the important thing is to participate, then it must also be important to participate in the work of
        avoiding participation. If anything can be considered experience, then the experience of not experiencing anything
        must also have value. Rather, nobody experiencing anything contrarily, could be a precious thing.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes14">14) School trips are simply a simulation of adult social life. If you ever go on
        a business trip with your boss, you won\'t get to choose where to stay or what to eat, but if you compromise, you
        can still have a modicum of fun. School trips train you to trick yourself into that kinda mindset.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes15">15) If this is all it takes to tear you apart, then maybe you weren\'t good friends at all.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes16">16) There are people who can\'t act unless they\'re faced with a problem. Unless
        they find their reason. All I was left with was the sinking suspicion that I\'d gone horribly wrong.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes17">17) What if, and this is strictly hypothetical, what if you could reload your
        save data to change your previous choice, like in a game? Would it change your life? The answer is
        a resounding no.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes18">18) It\'s arrogant to think just saying things out loud is enough. Self-gratifying on the part
        of the speaker, and conceited on the part of the listener. You won\'t always come to an understanding by talking things
        out.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes19">19) Expecting others to read your mind is delusional.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes20">20) It\'s not empty words I\'m after. There was something else I desired
        all along. Not mutual understanding, friendship, companionship, or anything of the sort. I don\'t care about being understood.
        I simply wish to understand. Understand, know, and rest easy in that knowledge, gain some peace of mind. Wanting to know people
        inside-out because being in the dark terrifies me is an awfully self-indulgent, egotistic, and arrogant wish. It\'s downright
        despicable and disgusting. Having a desire like that makes me sick to the stomach! But if it\'s at all possible to share that
        desire, if it\'s possible to have a relationship where you\'re free, to burden one another with that repulsive
        self-gratification… I know that it\'s out of the question! I know that it\'s out of my reach! Even so… Even so, I… I want
        something genuine.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes21">21) If wishes could be granted, if desires could be fulfilled, then
        I wouldn\'t wish or desire for anything after all. The things you\'re handed on a silver platter are never
        genuine, and never everlasting. And that is why I\'ll always keep searching.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes22">22) When people reach the halfway mark of a long ordeal, how do they feel? Does being
        only halfway there make them despair? Or do they feel relief at making it halfway there? Most people have to feel one
        way or the other, and both emotions create an opening in their hearts. That\'s why I pushed myself this far.</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes23">23) We all have our own personal image that\'s dictated by others, one that\'s always off the
        mark. We wish to remain true to ourselves, but who gets to decide who we are as people? When our image never goes hand-in-hand
        with reality, where can we find something genuine? Where can we find our true selves?</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes24">24) I don\'t want any vague answers or superficial relationships… Yeah, I\'m being stupid. I
        know that it\'s out of question. I know how this will end. I\'ll be left with nothing. Even so, I want us to think, writhe,
        struggle… and find… (something genuine).</string>
    <string name="hachimanQuotes25">25) It doesn\'t matter if we\'re wrong, because every time we go wrong, we\'ll
        continue to look for the right answer.</string>

    <string name="shizukaQuotesTitle">Hiratsuka Shizuka Quotes</string>
    <string name="shizukaQuotes1">1) Didn\'t anybody ever teach you not to bring up a girl\'s age?</string>
    <string name="shizukaQuotes2">2) Helping someone out is not a justifiable reason for you to get hurt.</string>
    <string name="shizukaQuotes3">3) You should realize that there are people whose hearts break each time they
        see you hurt yourself.</string>
    <string name="shizukaQuotes4">4) Getting into trouble is not a bad thing. It\'s proof that someone is watching
        you.</string>
    <string name="shizukaQuotes5">5) (To Hachiman) : If you stick to your ways, you won\'t be able to help somebody
        when you most want to.</string>
    <string name="shizukaQuotes6">6) People\'s thoughts don\'t always mirror how they feel. That\'s why they sometimes make
        decisions that seem nonsensical.</string>
    <string name="shizukaQuotes7">7) Don\'t understand? Then think more. If you can only think by calculating, then keep
        doing so until you can\'t. Think of all the answers you can and destroy them one by one with the process of elimination.
        Whatever remains is your answer.</string>
    <string name="shizukaQuotes8">8) If you could calculate feelings, then we\'d be in a digital age by now. The last
        remaining answer, the one you can\'t calculate… that\'s human emotion.</string>
    <string name="shizukaQuotes9">9) It is impossible to not hurt others. Humans unconsciously hurt others by simply existing.
        Whether you are alive or dead, you keep hurting people. Getting involved will hurt them, but trying not to get involved might
        hurt them too. But if it\'s someone you don\'t care about, you won\'t notice you\'ve hurt them. What\'s important is your awareness
        of it. It\'s because you care about them, that you feel like you\'ve hurt them. Caring about someone means being resolved to the
        fact that you\'ll hurt them. The more people care for each other, the farther out of reach certain things get. But that\'s not
        something to be sad about, I think it\'s probably something to be proud of.</string>
    <string name="shizukaQuotes10">10) The present isn\'t everything, but there are things you can only do now, things you can only
        find here. It\'s now. Now or never. Think, Writhe, Struggle and agonize. If not, what you are going through isn’t genuine.</string>
    <string name="shizukaQutoes11">11) Your impression of people is renewed every day. As you spend time with them and grow with them,
        you come to understand more.</string>
    <string name="shizukaQutoes12">12) People usually don\'t look back to see how far they\'ve come while they\'re still walking. Of
        course, when they come to a standstill, the more progress they\'ve made, the more betrayed they feel by their expectations.</string>

    <string name="othersQuotesTitle">Other Characters Quotes</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes1">1) (To Hachiman) How can you be so smart and yet not understand something simple? I
        never wanted to see something like that.</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes2">2) You see… I\'m in love with this club. I\'m in love…\n
        Anyway, like, if I become student council president, I can just half–ass things and our club will stay the same,
        right? We\'re talking about me here. Nobody is expecting anything from me. So… I\'m gonna beat Yukinon.</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes3">3) Once you lose something, it\'s gone forever.</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes4">4) You\'ve got it wrong. I told you, I\'m not as nice as a guy as you think I am.
        When I praise you, I do it for myself.</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes5">5) When you pick the only option you have to choose from, can you really call
        that your own decision?</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes6">6) (To Hachiman) Oh, that\'s so you. But you know, I\'m probably the only one who gets it. I\'ve lived
        with you my whole life, and that\'s why I can understand. That\'s why I can go \"what an idiot\" and shrug it off with a smile.
        I can think \"he\'s a lost cause\" and that\'d be that. Only I\'d still be a little sad. But it\'s not that simple for others.
        I\'m sure they\'re hurting \'cause they have no idea what you\'re thinking. You\'re nice to me, but you\'re only capable of that
        \'cause I\'m your sister, right? If I weren\'t, I bet you\'d stay as far away from me as possible.</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes7">7) Oni–chan, what are you saying? You dumbass! Nitwit!, Hachiman</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes8">8) Komachi -teki ni point ga takai.</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes9">9) People who can do everything flawlessly just aren\'t interesting at all, right?</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes10">10) (To Hachiman) Please take responsibility, okay?</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes11">11) What does it matter where I go? I haven\'t bothered anyone.</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes12">12) There\'s no girl who doesn\'t like homosexuality!</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes13">13) A Hayo x Hachi is a must buy! No… a must GAY!</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes14">14) Sore aru!</string>
    <string name="othersQuotes15">15) Yahallo!</string>


</resources>